MICHAEL LINDBERG

UX/UI DESIGNER/DEVELOPER
MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER

RELEVANT SKILLS

UX/UI DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

- WIREFRAMING
- MOCKUPS
- PROTOTYPING
- USER FLOWS
- PERSONAS
- UX RESEARCH METHODS
- ACCESSIBILITY
- CMS DEVELOPMENT
- AGILE WORKFLOW
- USER CENTERED DESIGN
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript/jQuery
- GIT VERSION CONTROL

ADOBE:

- ADOBE XD
- PHOTOSHOP
- ILLUSTRATOR
- INDESIGN
- AFTER EFFECTS
- PREMIERE PRO

VIDEO EDITING & COMPOSITING 3D MODELING & ANIMATION

GENERAL SKILLS

BILINGUAL ENGLISH/SPANISH
PROFESSIONAL COMMUNICATION
PROJECT MANAGEMENT
CUSTOMER SERVICE
TEAM PLAYER



PROFILE

I bring professional work experience and people skills together to accomplish tasks and solve problems. My approach is positive and hard working, regardless of the task or time available. I'm always striving to learn more and never stop progressing.

Online Portfolio: mlsk8r.github.io



WORK HISTORY

WEB DEVELOPER

SOUTHERN UTAH UNIVERSITY

08/2017 - PRESENT: Design, develop, and maintain the user experience and user interface of the university website for various campus partners/stakeholders using the Cascade CMS. Use the latest web standards and practices to enhance user experience and accessibility.

WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA

08/2016 - 08/2017: Develop and maintain websites for campus partners/stakeholders within the Drupal CMS as well as creating static websites outside of Drupal. Use the latest web standards and practices.

MULTIMEDIA SPECIALIST DIXIE STATE UNIVERSITY

08/2014 - 09/2016: Design, develop, and maintain the university website within the WordPress CMS. Additionally, create digital and print media in various forms for campus departments.

IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN DIXIE STATE UNIVERSITY

03/2013 - 08/2014: Provide IT support to campus staff and faculty members.

VFX/3D COMPOSITOR STEREO D LLC.

10/2010 - 11/2011: Create visual effects using composting & video editing software. Assistant team leader over a team of 8 artist.



EDUCATION

M.S. GRAPHIC INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY 2017 - 2019 4.0 GPA

B.S. COMPUTER INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY DIXIE STATE UNIVERSITY 2014 - 2016

ASSOCIATE OF ANIMATION AND VFX DAVE (Digital Animation & Visual Effects) SCHOOL 2009 - 2010 GRADUATED TOP 3 IN A CLASS OF 28

CONTACT

ONLINE PORTFOLIO



MCHL.LNDBRG@GMAIL.COM

MLSK8R.GITHUB.IO



435.705.9954